Let's see who dares kick me out
I'm carrying the Jiang family's blood
This is your grandson
Would you let him wander the streets?
Stop pretending
At your age
how could you even get pregnant?
We're at a hospital
How could I lie?
Son, I'm begging you
I'm already ruined
The Jiang family's only heir
Get up
I exposed my husband's affair with the maid
and was killed for it
This life
your whole family will pay in blood
Xiaolan, come on
Come wash my feet
Zhang Guifen, don't push it
Oh my
My precious son says
he wants grandma serving him personally
If she doesn't serve well
he won't come out
He'll just stay in there
Let's see who panics
You little sweetheart
Honey
Honey, calm down
Careful of the baby in her belly
If it weren't for the baby
carrying the Jiang family's blood
I'd have thrown you out already
Don't hurt the baby
Something's wrong
The way Jiang Chengang looked
that's not how you look at a daughter-in-law
Oh, Chengang
Gently now
I'm carrying your child
Don't crush it